http://www.swicofil.com/swicofil/company-information/organization/privacy

PRIVACY STATEMENT
The following is our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
Please read the following very carefully.
Swicofil AG values the privacy of our customers and takes reasonable measures to safeguard that information from unauthorized use. The following is a detailed explanation of our privacy policy with regard to the Swicofil web site. Please note we are not responsible for the information collection practices of those web sites that are linked to our site. You should review those sites privacy policies before submitting any private information.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
We do not systematically collect information. Even though if our website might use “cookies” we do never check those cookies. It is purely non-personal information about the visitors to our web site.
Personally identifiable information consists of information that is unique to you, such as credit card numbers, bank accounts, social security numbers, home address, email address and the like. This is the type of information that most people consider private and deem the most important to protect from unauthorized access.
Non-personally identifiable information most often consists of things such as how many times you have visited a particular web site, etc. This type of information is usually associated with a particular computer or IP address but not with a particular person. “Cookies” are pieces of information generated by a web server and stored in the user's computer.
Should you send us an email or fill in the inquiry form; we will then have access to personal information such as your name and email address. This is information which you willingly disclose and you know that you provided it to us.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY INFORMATION?
Swicofil does not lease, license, sell or share any of this information with anyone or any company except as mentioned in the proceeding paragraphs or in the paragraphs below. Only those employees that are responsible for handling your inquiries have access to your personal information. The only time someone other than a Swicofil employee will ever see your personal information is in the case of a judicial request or if the the supplier partner needs selected information to ensure a perfect service.
CAN I OPT OUT OF HAVING CERTAIN INFORMATION COLLECTED?
You have the option of disabling your computer’s ability to accept or transmit cookies.
NOTICE OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented. Please feel free to contact us if you should have any questions regarding this policy or to report a misuse of your personal information. Our responsible person can be reached at the general email address of Swicofil.
Looking for a product?
We love to serve you well.
Find Products
Looking for a product?
We love to serve you well.
Find Products
Looking for a product?
You have got a question?
We love to help you.
Contact us
You have got a question?
We love to help you.
Contact us
You have got a question?
×
ERROR
ERROR: Form not sent! Please fill in all necessary informations and click the Captcha Field
Close
